Arthur Trembley



cwan961115@gmail.com



+1 814 352 4892



linkedin.com/in/arthurtrembley-dai

Summary

As an expert in Full Stack Development, From 2015 I have worked in the famous software companies as Blockchain Developer, Al developer, Full Stack Software Engineer, Ecommerce Engineer, Project manager.

Provide my customers with the perfect front end and back end in which strong fashion and business style, gorgeousness and delicacy are in harmony.

Experience



🤼 Al Software Engineer & Project Manager

Dazzle Lab

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023 (3 months)

- As a Senior Al Engineer & Team manager, Building image generator, Education system, Booking system
- Mentored 5 developers with Python, Django, Flask, C++, Node, React, Vue, Angular

Ecommerce Developer & Project Manager

eagoats

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021 (7 months)

- I have got rich experience in building online stores by analyzing and monitoring customer experience and performing search engine optimization.
- Also, I could maximize my client's income by tracking store sales and customer visits.



Full Stack Blockchain Development

GetApp Group

Feb 2021 - May 2021 (4 months)

Have a working experience with NFT Marketplace, NFT Games, Crytpo Casino Games, Ecommerce, WooCommerce, Social Media Networks, Helthcare, Real Estate, Education, and have been involved in maintaining and management versions of source code using Github, Gitbuket, Jira, Asana.



Full Stack Developer

CANNAVIGIA

Sep 2020 - Jan 2021 (5 months)

- Ability to lead cross-functional team to realize the vision, taking into account business and technical requirements, constraints such as time, cost, and architecture tradeoffs.

- Highly organized, and efficient in a fast-paced, ever changing environments, able to prioritize effectively to accomplish objectives.

Blockchain Developer & Project Manager

NIPPON EXPRESS GROUP

Jul 2017 - Jun 2020 (3 years)

- I have rich experiences of building smart contracts for a lot of projects on various blockchain networks such as Ethereum, Binance Smart Cchain, polygon, Alorand, Solona, etc.
- Especially so far I have mostly kept on NFT crypto space like several kinds of games and NFT marketplace platforms using openzepplin ERC token standards like ERC-20, ERC-721, ERC-1155 tokens you know.

Full Stack Engineer

4K-Soft Ltd.

Sep 2015 - Jun 2017 (1 year 10 months)

- Worked with colleagues to set principles and patterns on the front-end and backend, design, develop, troubleshoot, debug, test, and ensure browser compatibility.
- Implemented professional code using PHP Framework, JavaScript Framework, CSS Framework, and Database Platform.
- Also consulted regularly with clients on project status, proposals, and technical issues

Education



The University of Tokyo

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Jul 2012 - Jun 2015

Skills

Content Management Systems (CMS) • E-Commerce • Artificial Intelligence (AI) • Blockchain • JavaScript Frameworks • PHP Frameworks • Databases • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Team Leadership • Project Management